SO I'VE SEEN
UNDER 950 SQUARE
FEET OR 50
PERCENT THE SIZE
OF YOUR EXISTING.
CORRECT.
THE WALL TOWNS,
THEY GET EATEN
BY THAT.
IT IS.
BUT TELL ME
ABOUT THE EXISTING
HOUSE THAT'S THERE.
IT'S PRETTY SMART.
IT'S 900 SQUARE
FEET NOW.
BUT DOES IT
HAVE A FULL
BASEMENT?
YES.
CAN YOU STAND
UP IN IT?
YES.
SO WE CAN
COUNT THAT SQUARE
FOOTAGE TOWARDS THE
CALCULATION, FINISHED OR
UNFINISHED, AS LONG
AS IT'S SIX
FOOT EIGHT FROM
THE CONCRETE FLOOR
TO THE BOTTOM
OF THE FLOOR
JOISTS.
I KNOW THEY
HAVE THE WASH
AND DRYER DOWN
THERE.
I HAVEN'T MEASURED
IT.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT
YOU NEED TO
MEASURE.
MEASURE FROM THE
CONCRETE FLOOR TO
THE FLOOR JOISTS.
IF YOU HAVE
ANYTHING OVER SIX
FOOT EIGHT, WE'RE
IN BUSINESS.
AND ALSO THEY
HAVE AN UPSTAIRS
BEDROOM.
DOES THAT COUNT
TOO?
YES.
AS LONG AS
IT'S SIX FOOT
EIGHT OR HIGHER.
OK.
YEAH.
THAT'S GOOD TO
KNOW.
YEAH.
SO WE'LL PROBABLY
BETWEEN